 movieQuestions[{
         "question": "What’s the name of the skyscraper in Die Hard?",
         "answers": ["Nakatomi Plaza", "Nakatomi Tower", "Nakatomi Building", "Nakatomi Place"],
         "correctAnswer": "Nakatomi Plaza",
     }

     {
         "question": "In which of his movies does Robert De Niro famously say “You talkin’ to me?”",
         "answers": ["Scar Face", "Taxi Driver", "Raging Bull", "Goodfellas"],
         "correctAnswer": "Taxi Driver",

     }

     {
         "question": "Which award winning director plays Korg in Thor: Ragnarok",
         "answers": ["Tim Burton", "J. J. Abrams", "Taika Waititi", "Anthony Rosso"],
         "correctAnswer": "Taika Waititi",

     }

     {
         "question": "Who is the only actor to receive an Oscar nomination for acting in a Lord of the Rings movie?",
         "answers": ["Elijah Wood", "Ian McKellen", "Andy Serkis", "Hugo Weaving"],
         "correctAnswer": "Ian McKellen",

     }

     {
         "question": "What song plays over the opening credits of Guardians of the Galaxy?",
         "answers": ["Come and Get Your Love", "Fox on the Run", "Oooh Child", "Hooked on a Feeling"],
         "correctAnswer": "Come and Get Your Love",

     }

     {
         "question": "Which Harry Potter star will be playing the dark knight in Matt Reeves upcoming movie 'The Batman'?",
         "answers": ["Tom Felton", "Daniel Radcliffe", "Matthew Lewis", "Robert Pattinson"],
         "correctAnswer": "Robert Pattinson",

     }

     {
         "question": "What is the highest-grossing movie of all time (not adjusted for inflation)?",
         "answers": ["Titanic", "Avatar", "Avengers Endgame", "Star Wars V"],
         "correctAnswer": "Avengers Endgame",

     }

     {
         "question": "For which one of these movies did Margot Robbie receive an oscar nomination?",
         "answers": ["Wolf of Wall Street", "I, Tonya", "Suicide Squad", "Once Upon A Time In Hollywood"],
         "correctAnswer": "I, Tonya",

     }

     {
         "question": "What was Quentin Tarantino‘s first feature as writer/director?",
         "answers": ["Jackie Brown", "Reservoir Dogs", "Pulp Fiction", "From Dusk Till Dawn"],
         "correctAnswer": "Reservoir Dogs",

     } {
         "question": "Which one of these Tim Burton films did composer Danny Elfman voice a character?",
         "answers": ["Bettle Juice", "Nightmare Before Christmas", "Planet of the Apes", "Frankenweenie"],
         "correctAnswer": "Nightmare Before Christmas",

     }
 ]

 tvQuestions[{
         "question": "Who has selective mutism in The Big Bang Theory?",
         "answers": ["Howard", "Amy", "Raj", "Stuart"],
         "correctAnswer": "Raj",
     }

     {
         "question": "What is Dexter Morgan's profession in the show 'Dexter'",
         "answers": ["Homicide Detective", "Blood Spatter Analyst", "Morgue Technician", "Barista"],
         "correctAnswer": "Blood Spatter Analyst",

     }

     {
         "question": "What actor plays Marty Byrde in 'Ozark'?",
         "answers": ["Jason Bateman", "Jerry O'Connell", "Nathan Fillion", "Liev Schreiber"],
         "correctAnswer": "Jason Bateman",

     }

     {
         "question": "In 'Master of None' where does Dev move to after being dropped from a big sci-fi movie?",
         "answers": ["France", "Spain", "Greece", "Italy"],
         "correctAnswer": "Italy",

     }

     {
         "question": "What actor plays 11 in the hit TV show 'Stranger Things'",
         "answers": ["Amelia Crouch", "Elle Fanning", "Chloë Grace Moretz", "Millie Bobby Brown"],
         "correctAnswer": "Millie Bobby Brown",

     }

     {
         "question": "Phil Coulson is a character portrayed by which actor in TV's 'Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.'?",
         "answers": ["Marc Evan Jackson", "Clark Gregg", "Alistair Petrie", "Colin Firth"],
         "correctAnswer": "Clark Gregg",

     }

     {
         "question": "In what U.S. state is Breaking Bad set?",
         "answers": ["New Mexico", "Virginia", "Arizona", "Oregon"],
         "correctAnswer": "New Mexico",

     }

     {
         "question": "Which one of this people do NOT appear in Netflix 'The Tiger King'?",
         "answers": ["Jeff Lowe", "Carole Baskin", "Joe Exotic", "Selina Kyle"],
         "correctAnswer": "Selina Kyle",

     }

     {
         "question": "Scrubs actor Zach Braff directed an episode of which award winning TV show about soccor?",
         "answers": ["Ted Lasso", "The Kicks", "All or Nothing", "Club of Crows"],
         "correctAnswer": "Ted Lasso",

     } {
         "question": "Brooklyn Nine Nine star Andy Samberg is also a member of which comedy band?",
         "answers": ["Tenacious D", "The Lonley Island", "Flight of the Conchords", "Spinal Tap"],
         "correctAnswer": "The Lonley Island",

     }
 ]

 playerArray = [{
         "name": "Martiless",
     },
     {
         "name": "Stevomar",
     },
     {
         "name": "Lilybells",
     },
     {
         "name": "Sparkimus",
     },
     {
         "name": "Golagol",
     } {
         "name": "Jon Snow",
     },
     {
         "name": "Tensoon",
     },
     {
         "name": "fast_and_the_curious",
     },
     {
         "name": "Mr Pink",
     },
     {
         "name": "Star Lord",

     }

 ]